http://www.thefirma.org/pages/privacy/

Privacy Statement
FIRMA is proud of its members, training programs, many industry partners, and good name…and we care about yours too.
We agree with progressive industry leaders that honoring and protecting customers' privacy is good business. We use secure servers to ensure all information given us is protected. If you access other sites through FIRMA's Web site links, we are not responsible for their policies so please make sure they are acceptable to you.
FIRMA does collect "site usage" information from all of our visitors to the FIRMA Web site. We collect IP addresses and/or domain names any time a page is requested from the server. The URL of a referring Web page also may be logged. We use this information to closely monitor what areas of the site are used most and how to determine which areas we need to improve.
FIRMA also collects information about our members, including your email address. In addition, information you agree to provide us when registering for a discussion forum, a seminar, surveys, or applying for membership, such as your name, title, company names, address, telephone number, fax number is collected. Our intention is always to gather only the information needed to serve you better and never to gather information without your knowledge. We do not and will not sell non-public information to any third party.
We do not spam. If you ever receive an email from us and have requested that you do not want your name on our list, please let us know, and we will take it off our mailing list.
As FIRMA grows and improves, with respect to industry trends and new technology tools, we are committed to updating our privacy policy promptly to keep you informed on how we use the information you give us.
If any User suspects FIRMA has handled its personal information in a manner that does not comply with this privacy statement, please contact us by e-mailing to thefirma@att.net or by calling (770) 790-8355.
© FIRMA 2016. All rights reserved.
Contact Us | Privacy Statement
The Fiduciary & Investment Risk Management Association, Inc.
P.O. Box 669515, Marietta, GA 30066
CONNECT WITH FIRMA
Search FIRMA
